

# Deepti Sharma

Web Developer

Skilled, passionate and a hardworking web developer with a keen eye for user experience and design. My goal is to design and develop interactive websites to further hone my web development skills. Experience in Learning and Development with an ability to communicate at all levels and associate with different cultures in an international environment.

- deepti.sharma@gmail.com
- Smørum, Denmark
- @DeeShaDK

- +45 5399 5902
- linkedin.com/in/deeptishrma
- github.com/Deepti-Dk

#### **EDUCATION**

### **ASP.NET MVC Web Development** Itucation, Denmark

01/2021 - I dag

Course contents:

- Web programming, C#, Microsoft Visual Studio 2019, ASP.NET MVC

## **Full Stack Web Development** Hack Your Future, Denmark

03/2020 - 01/2021

Course contents:

- HTML5, CSS5, JavaScript, MYSQL, NodeJS, React

#### UX

### ReDI Skole, Denmark

09/2020 - 12/2020

Course contents

 User research, Qualitative analysis, Quantitative analysis, Sketching, Content and UI, Wireframes, Testing

# Masters in Software Engineering

Punjabi University, India

08/2001 - 07/2003 Courses

- C, C++, Data Structures, Operating Systems, Management Information System, Computational Techniques, Software Engineering

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Teaching Assistant**

Børnehuset Tusindfryd, Denmark

09/2012 - 07/2020

# **Learning and Development Consultant**

Sun Life Financial Pvt. Ltd., India

09/2006 - 11/2011

#### IT Trainer

Rotherham General Hospital (NHS), U.K.

05/2004 - 12/2005

# **SKILLS**

HTML **CSS** Bootstrap JavaScript **ASP.NET MVC 5** DB/MYSQL NodeJS

#### **DEVELOPMENT TOOLS**

Microsoft Visual Studio 2019 Git Git Hub Postman Heroku Netlify Figma Knex.js

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

#### **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

GitHub User Search (11/2020 - 11/2020)

- Technologies used: HTML CSS JS MYSQL React and Netlify to deploy
- Project Link

Meal Sharing App (09/2020 - 10/2020)

- Technologies used: HTML CSS JS MYSQL React NodeJS and Heroku to deploy
- Project Link

#### **LANGUAGES**

**Enalish** 

Full Professional Proficiency

Danish

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi/Punjabi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency